{
    "subject": "resource/Jim_Webb",
    "predicate": "ontology/award",
    "object": "resource/Purple_Heart",
    "human_readable": "Jim Webb received a Purple Heart.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9777320027351379,
            "question": "For what action did Jim Webb receive a Purple Heart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9455474019050598,
            "question": "During which war or conflict did Jim Webb receive his Purple Heart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6510488390922546,
            "question": "What is a Purple Heart awarded for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.617390513420105,
            "question": "Are there any other notable individuals who have received a Purple Heart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3725673258304596,
            "question": "What is the significance of receiving a Purple Heart in American history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3384028673171997,
            "question": "What does the Purple Heart symbolize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2842622697353363,
            "question": "Were there any significant events in Jim Webb's life that led to him receiving this award?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26286810636520386,
            "question": "Is Jim Webb known for receiving military honors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1807132065296173,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Jim Webb's military service?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13734546303749084,
            "question": "What branch of the military did Jim Webb serve in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jim Webb received a Purple Heart.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6827_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Jim Webb's military service?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6827_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Jim Webb known for receiving military honors?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6827_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any significant events in Jim Webb's life that led to him receiving this award?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6827_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6827_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6827_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6827_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6827_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6827_131.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6827_162.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6827_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6827_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6827_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6827_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the requested format:\n\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Jim Webb received a Purple Heart. In fact, there are multiple mentions of Jim Webb being awarded the Purple Heart in different contexts and ceremonies."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that James K. Webb, referred to as Maj. James K. Webb, was awarded the Purple Heart during his service in Vietnam and again on a later occasion when he was injured. This supports the statement that Jim Webb received a Purple Heart."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}